<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Front page on PoppyGo Book</title><link>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/</link><description>Recent content in Front page on PoppyGo Book</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Site Workspace Configuration</title><link>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/docs/poppygo-app/30-site-configuration/1-workspace-conf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/docs/poppygo-app/30-site-configuration/1-workspace-conf/</guid><description>Site workspace configuration # Every PoppyGo website has it own workspace configuration file. It&amp;rsquo;s located in $HOME/Sukoh/config.websitename.json. The workspace configurations tells PoppyGo where to find the site files and where to publish the website. Normally this configuration needs no manual modification.
property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique name string mandatory The name of the website lastPublish integer mandatory Timespamp with time of last publication publishStatus integer mandatory 1=published, 2=publication pending remote source.</description></item><item><title>Accordion</title><link>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/docs/poppygo-app/30-site-configuration/2-content-model-configuration/field-types/accordion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/docs/poppygo-app/30-site-configuration/2-content-model-configuration/field-types/accordion/</guid><description>Accordion # The accordion field is a container field. It can define multiple input fields.
Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique title string mandatory The title of the accordion element dynFormSearchKey string optional key of one of the child field of which the value refers to a custom partial form dynFormObjectFile string with relative path to file without file extension optional if dynFormSearchKey is set this path points to the file containing a subform.</description></item><item><title>Boolean</title><link>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/docs/poppygo-app/30-site-configuration/2-content-model-configuration/field-types/boolean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://poppygo.github.io/poppygo-book/docs/poppygo-app/30-site-configuration/2-content-model-configuration/field-types/boolean/</guid><description>Boolean # The boolean field generated a switch. The output value is true or false
Boolean Properties # property value type optional description key string mandatory Keys are for internal use and must be unique title string mandatory The title of the element</description></item></channel></rss>